We hear family members and teachers telling us to "sit up straight" and "stand tall", but do they say that because an erect posture is more aesthetically pleasing, or is it the key to a pain-free back?
我们常听到家人和老师告诉我们"坐直"和"站直"，但他们这么说是因为挺拔的姿势在美学上更令人愉悦，还是它是背部无痛的关键？
It's commonly believed that 'slump' sitting or 'slouch' standing damages our spines.
人们普遍认为，弯腰坐着或懒散地站着会损害我们的脊柱。
But, is slouching really that bad?
但是，懒散的姿势真的那么糟糕吗？
Meghan Markowski, physiotherapist at Harvard-affiliated Brigham and Women's Hospital, says that a poor posture can lead to neck pain and back problems.
哈佛大学附属布里格姆妇女医院的物理治疗师梅根·马尔科夫斯基说，不良姿势会导致颈部疼痛和背部问题。
She also links it to other problems like poor balance, headaches and breathing difficulties.
她还将其与平衡能力差、头痛和呼吸困难等其他问题联系起来。
Meghan says we should aim for an upright spine position and to avoid flexing and arching our backs.
梅根说，我们应该以脊柱直立为目标，避免弯曲和拱起背部。
But, if you're a sloucher, there may be some good news coming from the last two decades of research…
但是，如果你是一个习惯懒散姿势的人，过去二十年的研究可能会带来一些好消息……
In an article called "Sit Up Straight: Time to Re-evaluate", physiotherapist Diane Slater and colleagues review the current research and conclude that there is no strong evidence that slouching aggravates back pain, or even that a perfect posture exists.
在一篇题为《坐直：是时候重新评估了》的文章中，物理治疗师黛安·斯莱特及其同事回顾了当前的研究，并得出结论：没有强有力的证据表明懒散的姿势会加重背痛，甚至也没有证据表明存在完美的姿势。
Instead, they argue that differences in our spinal curvatures are a fact of life, and that our backs are stronger than we think.
相反，他们认为，事实上现实生活中，我们脊柱曲度的是有差异的，我们的背部比我们想象的要强壮。
So, we're not sure that slouching causes back pain, but have you ever felt like slouching puts you in a worse mood?
所以，我们不确定懒散的姿势是否会导致背痛，但你有没有觉得懒散的姿势会让你心情更糟？
A 2014 study by Johannes Michalak and colleagues found that depressed participants in a slumped seated position remembered more negative words than positive, but this improved once they sat upright.
约翰内斯·米哈拉克及其同事在2014年的一项研究发现，处于低头弯腰坐姿的抑郁症参与者记住的负面词汇比正面词汇更多，但一旦他们坐直，情况就有所改善。
That means that the way we sit might make us feel more negative.
这意味着我们的坐姿可能会让我们感觉更消极。
Should we sit up straight and stand tall then?
那么，我们是否应该坐直站直呢？
Something both sides seem to agree on is that we should avoid staying in one static posture throughout the day – we should change positions and stretch.
双方似乎都同意的一点是，我们应该避免整天保持一种静态姿势——我们应该改变姿势并伸展身体。
The human spine is designed to be on the move and a sedentary lifestyle can increase the risk of back pain.
人类的脊柱是为活动而设计的，久坐不动的生活方式会增加背痛的风险。
If you're unable to do this, slouching in front of your computer all day may cause you discomfort, but the evidence tells us it's not actually damaging your spine.
如果你无法做到这一点，整天在电脑前弯腰驼背可能会让你感到不适，但证据告诉我们，这实际上并不会损害你的脊柱。